Another day, another line to say They're trying
to wash the real meat away But there's a fire, a
burning sound You can't keep a good thing down
It's a chain reaction I can't be contained
Starting up a fire That can't be explained A
chain reaction It's time to break them all A
story that's about to be told!
This plastic world is gonna crack. I'm never
ever looking back. I'm turning up my guitar
loud. I'm gonna stand out from the crowd. I can't
be contained. Starting up a fire that can't be
explained.
It's time to break the mold. A story that's about
to be told!
A chain reaction. I can't be contained.
Starting up a fire that can't be explained. A
chain reaction. It's time to break the mold. A
story that's about to be
told. Chain reaction.